大家好！
欢迎来到Steven唱歌时间
最近日子过得有点过于精彩了
心里有很多想说的东西
所以我写了一首歌
Oh，我会展示吉他谱，如果你想学的话
这是琴弦和标准音调
点代表手指
Ok，开始吧
歌名叫，Still Not Giving Up
你听说过臭名昭著的宝石战争吗
Hey there have you heard about the infamous Gem War
那发生在很久以前，我还未出生
Well it all started long before I was born
几千年的斗争，只为保护人类一族
Thousands of years of fighting to protect the human race
能坚持下来一定很难吧
It's been pretty tough keeping up the pace
我也承担了部分过错
I sure have made my fair share of mistakes
我不知Rose Quartz是一个大麻烦
I didn't know that Rose Quartz was such a big deal
有些伤痕连治愈能力也修复不了
There are some wounds that even healing powers can't heal
Oh～我感觉无能为力
Oh, I feel like I've messed up
魔法使命狠狠的打击了我
This magical destiny really kicked me in the butt
经历有好有坏
We've had some good times and some pretty bad luck
但我们仍在一起
But we're still in this together
而且我们并未退缩
And we're still not giving up
我们并未退缩
We're still not giving up
我并未退缩
I'm still not giving up
Da da da da da
Da da da da da da
Da da da
谢谢观看
如果最近过得不开心，试试写歌吧
我很愿意听
Ok，I love you，bye！